Marlon Riggs Papers, 1957-1994 M1759
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3: Other Papers
  - Subseries 3: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 75, Folder 21)
      Robert Flaherty Seminars/International Film Seminars organisation, 1988-1991
    - Program and information from The 34th Robert Flaherty Seminar, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Program and information from The 35th Robert Flaherty Seminar, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Program and information from The 36th Robert Flaherty Seminar, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Information from the Foundation Center Network (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence from and information about the Funding Exchange, 1991-2 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Information about Getty Center funding (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Harvard Gay & Lesbian Newsletter, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Information packet from the Humanities Research Institute Minority Discourse program, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence from FAF, Film Arts Foundation, 1985/6 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Information from Image Transform, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence from ITVS, Independent Television Service, 1991/2 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - INPUT 88 conference, Philadelphia, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and newsletters (Box 76, Folder 9)
      International Documentary Association, 1988/90
    - International Documentary Association Newsletter, Vol.4 Nos 1-3 1985 and Feb and April 1992 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Information about Channel 32 KMTP-TV, Minority Television Project, 1991-2 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (Box 76, Folder 12)
      Media Alliance (NY), 1992
    - Correspondence (Box 76, Folder 13)
      Minority Television Project, 1993
    - Correspondence (Box 76, Folder 14)
      Museum of Broadcast Communications, 1995
    - Miscellaneous Media Organizations (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (Box 76, Folder 16)
      National Alliance of Media Arts Centers, 1991
    - Correspondence (Box 76, Folder 17)
      National Asian American Telecommunications Association, 1989-1993
    - Correspondence (Box 76, Folder 18)
      National Black Media Coalition, 1984-86
    - Editions of 'MediaLine', Vol.7 Nos 1 & 2, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence from the (Box 76, Folder 20)
      National Black Programming Consortium, 1987
    - Information from the National Coalition of Independent Public Broadcasting Producers, 1988-90 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 1)
      National Coalition of Multi-Cultural Media Arts, 1989-90
    - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 2)
      National Cultural Alliance, 1993
    - Final report (Box 77, Folder 3)
      National Minority Programming Task Force, 1989
    - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 4)
      National Task Force on AIDS Prevention, BWMT, 1990
    - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 5)
      New York Council for the Humanities, 1988
    - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 6)
      Oakland Men's Project, 1992
    - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 7)
      Organization of American Historians, 1987-1990
    - Organization of American Historians, Program of the 81st Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 9)
      Other Countries organization, 1993
    - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 10)
      'The Paulina Project', 1992
    - Correspondence and news (Box 77, Folder 11)
      PBS, Public Broadcasting Service, 1993
    - PBS Expense forms and reports, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - PBS, National Program Policy Committee (Box 77, Folder 13)
      Meeting minutes and reports, 1987-1992
    - Correspondence and information (Box 77, Folder 14)
      Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1989
    - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 15)
      San Francisco Art Institute, 1993
    - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 16)
      Third World Newsreel, 1992
    - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 17)
      Video Association of Dallas, 1993
    - 4 Telephone Message pads, 1988-1990, spiral bound (Flat-box 152)
    - 7 Telephone Message pads, 1990s, spiral bound (Flat-box 173)
    - 9 Telephone Message pads, 1990s, spiral bound (Flat-box 176)
    - General Correspondence - Business, 1987-1990 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence - Business, 1991 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence - Business, 1992 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence - Business, 1992-1993 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence - Personal (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence - Personal (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 4: Personal Papers
    - Riggs filofax (Flat-box 47)
      Information for the year 1991. Diary only contains written information, all other aspects of filofax are blank.
    - Riggs Rolodex with business and personal address cards (Flat-box 48)
    - Photographs of Riggs-1970s (Half-box 54, Folder 1)
    - Poloroid of Riggs, also poloroid of Riggs 's sister Sacha's dog Tanya, no dates (Half-box 54, Folder 2)
    - Photograph of Riggsand his mother, Berlin 1990 (Half-box 54, Folder 3)
    - Postcards to Riggs (Flat-box 63, Folder 1)
      from various people
    - Christmas cards to Riggs (Flat-box 63, Folder 2)
    - Get Well cards to Riggs (Flat-box 63, Folder 3)
    - General cards to Riggs (Flat-box 63, Folder 4)
    - Birthday cards to Riggs (Flat-box 63, Folder 5)
    - Letters to Riggs (Flat-box 63, Folder 6)
    - Various receipts and miscellaneous papers (Flat-box 63, Folder 7)
    - Riggs' Notebook (Flat-box 64, Folder 1)
      Journalism, some shorthand
    - Riggs' Notebook - (Flat-box 64, Folder 2)
      Journalism notes, spiral bound notebook, 1979
    - Riggs' Notebook (Flat-box 64, Folder 3)
      Journalism notes, spiral bound notebook, 1980
    - Riggs' Notebook, 1980 (Flat-box 64, Folder 4)
      Journalism notes, spiral bound notebook, including notes about Oakland Blues project
    - Riggs' Notebook, 1982 (Flat-box 64, Folder 5)
    - Riggs' Diary, 1984 (Flat-box 64, Folder 6)
    - Riggs' Diary, 1987 (Flat-box 65, Folder 1)
    - Riggs' Diary, 1985 (Flat-box 65, Folder 2)
    - Harvard and Radcliffe, Class of 1978, Fifteenth Anniversary Report (Flat-box 65, Folder 3)
    - Perversion, book of poetry by Roy Gonsalves, signed by author to Riggs (Flat-box 65, Folder 4)
    - Guest book, various signatures, unknown event, 16 May 1991 (Flat-box 65, Folder 5)
    - Riggs' Cowl for Honorary Doctor of Arts, California College of Arts and Crafts, 1993 (Flat-box 66)
    - Poster of Lyle Harris exhibition, signed by Lyle Harris, to Riggs, 1993 (Flat-box 67, Folder 1)
    - Letter to Riggs from Les Turner, 1991 (Flat-box 67, Folder 2)
    - Envelope of writings to Riggs from Mark Harvey, Richmond, Virginia, 1992 (Flat-box 67, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence to Riggs, 1977-78 (Flat-box 67, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence to Riggs, 1982-1985 (Flat-box 67, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence to Riggs, 1987-1989 (Flat-box 67, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence to Riggs, no dates (Flat-box 67, Folder 7)
    - ID cards (Flat-box 67, Folder 8)
      Arizona driving license, Boston Library Card, Harvard Student card etc, 1970s
    - Desk Diary 1992 (Flat-box 67, Folder 9)
    - Get Well cards (Flat-box 85)
      To Riggs from various people, also postcards and invitations/thank you cards, 1980s
    - Birthday and Christmas cards (Flat-box 86)
      To Riggs from various people, 1980s, also Riggs 's 1982 Diary and Personal notebook, 1982, and leather notebook, also filofax diary pages from 1989
    - Get Well cards (Flat-box 159)
      To Riggs from various people, also postcards and invitations/thank you cards, 1990s
    - Personal Correspondence 1 (Half-box 171, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence 2 (Half-box 171, Folder 2)
    - Personal Letters (Half-box 171, Folder 3)
    - Personal File - Notes from hospital stays (Half-box 171, Folder 4)
    - Qual Med - Hospice Information (Half-box 171, Folder 5)
    - Lilienthal and Fowler - Will Information (Half-box 171, Folder 6)
    - Funeral (Half-box 171, Folder 7)
    - Sascha's Stories (Half-box 171, Folder 8)
    - Joey2 - story, typed (Half-box 214, Folder 1)
    - St Agnes School Directory, 1980-81, Sascha Riggs attending (Half-box 214, Folder 2)
    - personal letter to Riggsfrom Michael Oatis, 1988 (Half-box 214, Folder 3)
    - Personal - Riggs Clippings (Half-box 214, Folder 4)
    - Riggs Bio (Half-box 214, Folder 5)
    - Riggs Schedule (Half-box 214, Folder 6)
    - Riggs Internships Info (Half-box 214, Folder 7)
    - Harvard Letters (Half-box 214, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Minority program Info (Half-box 214, Folder 9)
    - Grades/Transcript (Half-box 214, Folder 10)
    - Riggs Celebration flyers, 1994 (Half-box 214, Folder 11)
    - The James Baldwin Award (Flat-box 225)
      Presented to Riggs at the 4th National Gay & Lesbian Leadership Conference, 1991
    - Sylvester Arts Action Award (Flat-box 225)
      Presented to Riggs at the San Francisco Black Coalition on AIDS, 1991
    - National Gay & Lesbian Task Force Policy Institute Award, 1991 (Flat-box 225)
      Honor award presented to Riggs at the 4th Annual Creating Change Conference by the National Gay & Lesbian Task Force Policy Institute, 1991
    - Deframed pictures from Riggs wall, personal drawings (Flat-box 226)
    - Material items (Flat-box 240)
      sheet backdrop with graffitti, tshirt with 'Silence=Death' logo, cloth bag from the 6th Annual National Black Gay and Lesbian conference 1992
  - Subseries 5: Financial Papers
    - Expenses claims and invoices for Ethnic Notions (Flat-box 15, Folder 1)
    - Expenses claims and invoices for Tongues Untied (Flat-box 15, Folder 2)
    - Expenses claims and invoices for Tongues Untied (Flat-box 15, Folder 3)
    - Expenses claims and invoices for Anthem (Flat-box 15, Folder 4)
    - Expenses claims and invoices for Affirmations (Flat-box 15, Folder 5)
    - Expenses claims and invoices for Color Adjustment (Flat-box 15, Folder 6)
    - Expenses claims and invoices for BIBA (Flat-box 15, Folder 7)
    - Expenses claims and invoices for No Regret (Flat-box 15, Folder 8)
    - Ethnic Notions expenses claims (Flat-box 37, Folder 1)
      Receipts for copying, postal services, trip to New York, processed cheque payments, and personal diary - 1983
    - Deposit slips and books, Central Bank, 1979-1981 (Flat-box 37, Folder 2)
    - Invoices from the Law office of Peter Franck, San Francisco, for services, 1991 (Flat-box 37, Folder 3)
    - Invoice from Angela Davis for replacement to glass doors - paid by Marlon (Flat-box 37, Folder 4)
    - Expenses 1988 - various receipts (Flat-box 37, Folder 5)
    - Expenses 1986 - various receipts for Ethnic Notions (Flat-box 37, Folder 6)
    - Ethnic Notions donations slips (Flat-box 37, Folder 7)
    - Central Bank statements, 1979-1981 (Flat-box 38, Folder 1)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      Restricted
    - Citibank statements, Dec 1991 to Dec 1992 (Flat-box 38, Folder 2)
    - Citibank transactions, 1991 (Flat-box 38, Folder 3)
    - Citicorps Statements, 1989 (Flat-box 38, Folder 4)
    - Visa Credit Card Statements, Household Credit Services, 1991-1992 (Flat-box 38, Folder 5)
    - American Express statements, 1991-1992 (Flat-box 38, Folder 6)
    - Mastercard Statements, National Credit Group, 1991-1992 (Flat-box 38, Folder 7)
    - Bank of America statements, 1991 (Flat-box 38, Folder 8)
    - Car Loan Statements, Credit Union, 1991 (Flat-box 38, Folder 9)
    - Mobil Oil Credit card statements, 1991 (Flat-box 38, Folder 10)
    - Income received and remittance cheques for project work, 1991 (Flat-box 41, Folder 1)
    - UC, Berkeley Paystubs, 1991 (Flat-box 41, Folder 2)
    - Tax information paperwork, 1991 (Flat-box 41, Folder 3)
    - California Newsreel Invoices for Ethnic Notions, 1990 and 1991 (Flat-box 41, Folder 4)
    - Car Insurance coverage and DMV registration, 1991 (Flat-box 41, Folder 5)
    - Color Adjustment expenses claims, 1990 (Flat-box 41, Folder 6)
    - Invoices for film and video supplies and transfers, 1991 (Flat-box 41, Folder 7)
    - Invoices and expenses, 1990 (Flat-box 41, Folder 8)
    - Signifyin Works General Fund invoices and expenses, 1991 (Flat-box 41, Folder 9)
    - Color Adjustment disbursements log/copies of invoices, 1991 (Flat-box 41, Folder 10)
    - Invoices (Flat-box 41, Folder 11)
      From Deborah Hoffman, Christiane Badgley, Anna Vega, Nicole Atkinson, Michele Zaccheo, and Mark Landsman for services rendered on the Color Adjustment project, 1991
    - Invoices from Akiba Timoya for services rendered, 1991 (Flat-box 41, Folder 12)
    - Various invoices for services and supplies, mostly for Color Adjustment, 1991 (Flat-box 41, Folder 13)
    - Payroll, ADP (Automatic Data Processing), 1992 (Flat-box 42, Folder 1)
    - Payroll, ADP (Automatic Data Processing), 1993 (Flat-box 42, Folder 2)
    - Payroll, ADP (Automatic Data Processing), 1994 (Flat-box 42, Folder 3)
    - General Fund, Signifyin Works, Bank Statements, 1994 (Flat-box 42, Folder 4)
    - 1983 Paycheck stubs (Half-box 59, Folder 1)
    - 1984 Paycheck stubs (Half-box 59, Folder 2)
    - Taxes 1981 (Half-box 59, Folder 3)
    - Taxes 1982 (Half-box 59, Folder 4)
    - Taxes 1983 (Half-box 59, Folder 5)
    - Taxes 1985 (Half-box 59, Folder 6)
    - Taxes 1986 (Half-box 59, Folder 7)
    - Taxes Paid 1984 (Half-box 59, Folder 8)
    - Income 1985 (Half-box 59, Folder 9)
    - Income 1986 (Half-box 59, Folder 10)
    - Income 1987 (Half-box 59, Folder 11)
    - Taxes 1989 (Half-box 59, Folder 12)
    - Taxes 1990 (Half-box 59, Folder 13)
    - Accountant (Half-box 59, Folder 14)
    - Invoices conferences and festivals (Half-box 59, Folder 15)
    - Taxes 1992 (Half-box 59, Folder 16)
    - Taxes 1993 (Half-box 59, Folder 17)
    - UC, Berkeley Benefits - medical (Half-box 59, Folder 18)
    - UC, Berkeley Benefits - retirement (Half-box 59, Folder 19)
    - Citicorps Money Market Savings account statements, 1984-87 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Citicorp Personal Checking Account statements and receipts, 1984-87 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Harvard Loan Correspondence (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Harvard Loan Repayment Statements (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - CA State Credit Union statements, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Transamerican Car Insurance, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Jensen and Conklin Insurance, 1984/5 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Tongues Untied Citicorp Bank Statements (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Color Adjustment NYCH account statements, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Color Adjustment Gerbode account statements (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Color Adjustment Gerbode account statements (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Color Adjustment General Fund, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Color Adjustment CPB account statements, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Color Adjustment Rockefeller account statements, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Color Adjustment NEA account statements, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Color Adjustment NEA account statements, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Color Adjustment CCH account statements, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Color Adjustment NEA invoices, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Color Adjustment Gerbode invoices, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Color Adjustment CPB invoices, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Color Adjustment CPB invoices, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Color Adjustment NEA Invoices, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Color Adjustment AFI invoices paid, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Color Adjustment AFI invoices, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Citicorp bank book - deposits and debits, 1985-86 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - 1983 diary (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Notebook of expenses, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - 1986 desk calender (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Harvard Correspondence (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Harvard Scholarship/Loans (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Harvard Club of San Francisco (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Harvard Interviews (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Oakland museum (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Susan Noon File (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - The Fox Theater, Oakland, Project proposal (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Power Rector Productions - The State of the Language (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - WIN Program letter of thanks (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous memorabilia (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Wine Country' Transcript (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Peter Webster checks (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Riggs Medical expenses/bills, 1989/90 (Flat-box 91, Folder 1)
      Restrict
    - Invoices for services rendered from Bob Paris and Akiba Timoya, 1990/91 (Flat-box 91, Folder 2)
    - 1988 expenses list (Flat-box 91, Folder 3)
    - 1989/90 income receipts (Flat-box 91, Folder 4)
    - Notes on Taxes, 1989 (Flat-box 91, Folder 5)
    - Restricted: Riggs, Bills Paid - Various bills and invoices, 1989/90 (Flat-box 104, Folder 1)
    - Restricted: Credit Card statements, 1988/9 (Flat-box 104, Folder 2)
    - Restricted: 1984 Tax Receipts (Flat-box 104, Folder 3)
    - Restricted: Bank Statements, 1990 (Flat-box 104, Folder 4)
    - Restricted: Miscellaneous deposit slips, 1970s (Flat-box 104, Folder 5)
    - Checking accounts information (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - In kind contributions reports (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - CPB: Unsolicited proposals for Program Fund (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - CPB Program Fund (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Budget examples (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Documentary Research Inc (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Eastman Fund (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - FAF Funding Application (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Film Fund (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - Film Fund Applications (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Film Fund Grant (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Film Arts Foundation Fundraising Seminar (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - Focus productions (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - Foundations Lists (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - Interregional Program service (Box 196, Folder 15)
    - MFH - Massachusetts Foundation for the Humanities (Box 196, Folder 16)
    - National Community Funds (Box 196, Folder 17)
    - NEA: Performance Reports (Box 196, Folder 18)
    - NEA: Letters (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - NEA: Application (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - NEA: Invoices (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - NEH: Grants (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - NEH: Invoices (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - NEH: Letters (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - NEH: Application 1983 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - NEH: Proposal 1983 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - NEH: Proposal 1984 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - NEH: Proposal 1986 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - NYCH: Grant (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - NYCH: Performance (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - NYCH: Proposal (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Pioneer Fund (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Rocky Mountain Film Center (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - Zellerbach Fund (Box 197, Folder 16)